

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

CONTACT

github.com/ralodev/

contact@ralo.dev

México

<u>ralo.dev</u>

SUMMARY

I'm a Full Stack Developer with more than 1 year of experience in web development. I'm adept at contributing to highly collaborative work environment, finding solutions and determining customer satisfaction. Passionate programmer with drive to learn and master new technologies.

LANGUAGES

Spanish Native
English C1 (TOEFL Certified)

EDUCATION

BS. COMPUTER
SYSTEMS ENGINEERING

National Technological Institute of Mexico, Oaxaca Campus

2018 - 2023

SKILLS

- Spring Boot
- Vue.js, React
- Java, JavaScript, HTML, CSS
- PostgreSQL, MySQL, MongoDB
- Git, GitHub, GitLab
- · Heroku, Netlify, GCloud, AWS
- Interpersonal Skills
- Effective Communication

WORKING EXPERIENCE

SOFTWARE ENGINEER FREELANCE

Multiple platforms AUG 2023 - PRESENT

- Instructing on requirements gathering methodologies and documentation.
- Teaching several courses on web development.
- Providing guidance on technologies and tools to use.

FULL STACK DEVELOPER INTERN

Technologial Institute of Oaxaca | AUG 2022 - JUL 2023

- Optimized report generation times by 90%
- Developed a fully functional HRMS using Spring Boot and Vue.js
- Successfully deployed and mantained the HRMS hosted at https://itoaxaca.tech

TOURISTIC AMBASSADOR

SECTUR Oaxaca JUN 2019 - AUG 2019

- Multilingual Communication: Facilitating communication between visitors and locals
- Logistics and Organization: Planning and coordinating activities



Check out my portfolio to see more about me